Do you have food?
I am starving to death....
Let your hair down and relax
You don't look like a boy.
Open your hair and relax
I'm not afraid.
Travelers talked about the
hero Robin Hood in these hills.
He was protecting the weak.
No one protects the weak.
And he wasn't a hero.
He prayed three times a day
and gave silver to the poor.
And he had Lady Marian's love.
Isn't he a hero?
Lady Marian. unfortunately
A story drunker than me
by the narrator.
Taken from an old shepherd's tale.
She was Robin Hood's great love.
To such a man
There is no such thing as great love.
I know who met this man...
Want a little secret?
I would like.
once in your life
He didn't even pray.
These tales spread throughout the country.
Lie upon lie.
He was a murderous bandit.
Maybe someone who slit the
throat of a sheriff and many others.
people nothing
They saw meaning where there was none.
He wasn't a hero.
He robbed and killed for pleasure.
It didn't get more than that.
These people you met.
Did they say he was
remorseful for his crimes?
I suspect you're feeling tired.
If you meet this Robin Hood man
know that;
You must hurry and take
care of your remaining life here.
Translated into Turkish;
ufukbaba
Let's see who your relatives are?
William Wainwright of Pickering.
Pickering?
Your father?
Your grandfather?
You should take a bath and get rid of your scent.
Or you should have waited for the wind to change.
Or you should have shifted
your weight to your back foot.
That's all... you did it wrong.
DEATH OF ROBIN HOOD
They are telling lies.
These stupid ordinary people.
Lies about his heroism and goodness.
But there are blood debts to be paid.
And generations of victims haunt him.
Because in reality. none of them
killer bandit
than Robin Hood
they were not bad and more sought after.
And from his Little John.
Talk to Thomas.
He was hanged in the South.
Will?
They destroyed that too.
I have no one else to ask.
What happened?
My name is Edward.
Who was Edward?
We met him on the
road 10 summers ago.
His brother had died and he was
going to grow rye and peas on his land.
Nobody Edward's He
didn't know his face.
So I killed him.
Edward is mine now.
And Margaret is a good wife.
A good farm.
What happened?
A family on the land
found me He took my
farm. he took my Margaret.
They tried to take my life.
I can't take back
what's mine alone.
It's not yours.
This is my family.
I'm so tired. John.
Edward
I'm so tired. Edward.
This will be a very tough battle.
One that will go down in stories.
- Are they strong?
- Yes.
They come from an old family.
They say they
are of Viking blood.
There is a story that their
grandfather once fought a bear.
It's going to be a huge war. Robin.
How many people are there?
Four... five.
Together we can beat them.
We will most likely die.
Turkish subtitles;
ufukbaba / opensubtitles.org
ufukbaba
opensubtitles.com
Turkish subtitles;
ufukbaba / opensubtitles.org
ufukbaba / opensubtitles.com
Robin.
Fred.
It's a good adventure.
When we meet the potter. do we see him naked?
Did we leave it or kill
it. do you remember?
When I tried to tell the story
someone said we left him naked.
I couldn't remember exactly.
You always explained this well. Robin.
Why would we leave him naked?
I don't know.
We just...
- We have never met a Potter.
- What do you mean we've never met him?
So this never happened. It's just
a story you've heard somewhere.
But if we met a potter.
we killed him.
If there was a story.
I would remember it.
Yes.
Tell me about your wife.
Margaret.
She's a good woman.
She is a very good woman.
It teaches me to pray for us.
Draw a portrait of yourself.
Should I draw a portrait of you?
Drawing a portrait.
Her hair... red.
What Red?
Red like fresh blood.
No. no.
Something red and good.
It's like something...
Like the setting sun.
Like the setting summer sun.
Margaret is a good wife.
With her red hair like
the setting summer sun.
he cares about me
I'm interested in that too.
Robin.
Open land stretches beyond the mountains...
There are many
places to start over.
I don't plan on starting again.
I aim for a righteous death.
Come on!
Hendri!
No. Hendri!
Run!
Run No... -Hendri!
- Come on!
Hendri. bring the others!
Edward!
- Edward.
My love!
Take care of little Margaret.
You are safe.
You're safe. girl.
Let's pray.
O Lord our God.
Give us the grace to desire
you with all our hearts. pray now.
And when we find you. we can love you And in
loving you. we can hate the
sins from which you saved us.
For the sake of Jesus Christ.
Amine.
Good morning my baby.
I am sad.
It was like this when I woke up.
Cousin.
I am sad!
We cry to O'Lord.
Have mercy on
us... and forgive us.
O King of heaven and Eternal Lord.
receive our prayers that we pour out
And make us ask for forgiveness
The patient. the prisoner. emerges.
Help the widow and the orphan.
And make us ask for forgiveness.
We sinned and left you
You. Savior of all.
save us... and forgive us.
Have mercy on those who repent.
And wash away the stains of sin.
And make us ask for forgiveness.
Amine.
Godwyn!
Please...
Margaret?
Margaret!
NO!
John!
Little John!
Twenty winters ago...
You killed my cousin Walter of Hathersage
Now you have killed my son and my grandson.
As Weregild. I will accept your
life and that of your daughter.
NO!
Robin?
I've heard stories of
a hidden monastery.
There is a Priest there who
is older than anyone knows.
It has a healing spell.
I will take you to him.
He will make you well again.
I've heard incredible stories.
Robin.
we need to go
They will hunt us.
Look at the snow.
It's strange that it dropped so late.
But it will stay on the ground.
The Lord's back is turned.
A man brought you here.
He sealed his wounds with
fire. And he didn't do a bad job.
You've been here for six days.
You have sores on your abdomen.
Your ribs and leg are badly broken.
Do you understand my words?
Yes.
You are in the Monastery of St.
Clement.
It's a place where you
can heal. So which town?
There is no town.
Do you know the story of Saul?
What?
Here once upon a time
There was a man
named Saul who was
threatening God's disciples.
He came to the prince of priests.
and asked him for letters to Damascus.
To synagogues; If he meets any man or
woman of this path. so that he may bind them...
That's all we have to do.
Just a few drops.
Wasn't it very painful?
It wasn't.
I'm Sister Brigid.
What is your name?
Randolph.
I owe you an apology. Randolph.
What apology?
You begged me to let you die.
And I didn't.
- You said it was true.
- I had a fever.
Your fever is gone.
Rest now. Randolph.
Your body is covered in scars.
You mean anyone
who harms the cult?
I do not.
Will any harm follow you here?
It won't happen.
You will not harm them.
Now let's go back to bed.
Now let's get back to the door.
Now open the door.
Go as far as you want.
Can you row now?
There's a boat on the west coast.
No problem.
You can stay here if
you help in the orchard.
I am not a farmer.
- So you don't know how to hunt?
- Yes. I know how to hunt.
There is a game on this island.
But no. you can't hunt.
You can't even draw the bow.
- I can draw my bow
- Mostly rabbits.
- Do you know how to trap?
- I know how to trap you.
It's nice. but there are no more than six traps.
Otherwise their population cannot survive.
Can you manage the six traps?
I can manage six traps.
Good morning my baby.
And for the rest of your time.
You can help in the orchard.
Are you trying to escape?
You are so quiet.
I am quiet and slow.
You are quiet too. but
you need to be slow.
- You are disabled.
- Oh. you are a leper.
It's okay to be slow.
We are safe here.
This is a very bold statement.
You are aware of this. right?
I know.
Because it kept us safe.
Your nun?
He was just like us.
He knew great sadness and great pain.
Young widow.
But through this sadness he
found the strength to heal us.
You don't look like you're getting better.
The Mother Superior once told
me the story of a great philosopher.
The greatest philosopher of his time.
But one day. his
king opposed him.
He threw him into the dungeon
to be tortured and executed.
But in his misery...
While he had nothing. an angel came
to the Philosopher and talked to him.
And because all you have is death
He learned that it doesn't matter.
Because he had something that
could never be touched or taken away.
He had a mind.
And in his mind
He had a God.
It's never too late to find peace.
What are you doing?
I row every day.
Your friend was strong enough to bring you.
but not everyone is. so I'm carrying them.
- Can you take me across?
- I won't.
When you are stronger
you can row yourself.
Your tasks for now
work on it.
I think you were setting a trap.
- I will hunt.
No. you can't hunt.
Leper.
What happened to that great philosopher?
Of course he was
tortured and executed.
Certainly.
Hey!
He brought a leper.
from the far shore.
My father died.
How's the girl?
Let me show you my trees.
These are elderberries.
Harvest is done in late summer.
Do you know what happened before this?
You'll have to choose
this side so I can hear it.
Pears. I harvest immediately after...
So what was I before this?
A gunslinger at best.
Absolutely at best.
We have our own style.
Do you remember trees?
- Pear and Elderberry.
- Wonderful.
Some people know...
But the abbot doesn't
care who we are.
And apples are harvested in the fall.
He... tell me about what happened to him?
The nun takes care of the girl.
If you're worried you
should talk to him.
What were the trees?
Pears. apples and elderberries.
Wonderful.
This will be your last blood draw;
Your body still needs a lot of healing. though.
You look tired.
I am.
But I've been tired before.
The child is not sleeping.
What happened to him?
Terrible things.
- Did he tell you his story?
- No. he doesn't talk.
He doesn't eat. he doesn't sleep.
What's its name?
Margaret.
Who's that?
I met his father...
A farmer.
Well...he is dead.
- It seems so.
- What about his mother?
I think he died.
I don't know. Dead past.
Was he killed?
Maybe.
You lie very well.
Did the child see it?
He may have seen it.
Too much for a child to see.
I'm sorry about your friend.
Thank you.
Do you want me to pray for him?
However you like.
What was its name?
Edward
Do not be afraid in your heart. for you
believe in God and you also believe in me.
There are many rooms
in my father's house.
And when I have prepared a place for
you. I will come and take you to myself.
Because wherever I
am. you can be there too.
And wherever I go.
you will know the way.
-Margaret!
- He stabbed me!
Margaret.
No problem.
Margaret!
It's okay. Margaret.
No problem..
He doesn't know this
candidate. There are pigs around.
Margaret!
Hey!
Give it to me.
Give it!
Those men who hurt you...
Do they know you're here?
What's my name?
Say my name.
Randolph.
This is true.
Who is Little John?
This name is bullshit and
you should never say it.
And if you tell. a cat will come
at night and take your tongue.
No problem.
Go to sleep now.
I will watch the storm.
It's okay. they know.
Close your eyes.
You can sleep.
Sleep.
Thank you for bringing him back.
It was nothing.
Do you know the story of this Order?
No.
In prehistoric times. this was a
sacred place for the ancient Druids.
They worshiped unknown gods.
They were worshiped in these forests.
Then the Romans came. felt the magic
of this place and
built their temples.
And people felt it too.
They came here to worship.
Countless gods.
from tribe to tribe. did
not even know how
to talk to each other.
But still we are all
drawn to this place.
Do you believe there
is Magic on this island?
I believe there is power in this.
I saw the power in stories.
They can be used to
make men do terrible things.
And then these terrible things
become stories and stories...
No.
You can't trust any of them.
We cannot trust them.
Knives cut bread
as well as meat.
It's a matter of balance.
Does balance have a say?
I think we wouldn't be here if
the balance didn't have a say.
This world wouldn't exist here...
and we couldn't share these words.
Have you ever thought about this?
Incredible precision of balance.
over such a wide period of time.
The balance it takes to create a
word. any word that
can pass between lips.
It must be understood by two minds.
Randolph.
Thank you.
Aren't you hungry?
No?
I will die soon.
How do you know?
I could feel it inside me.
What does it feel like?
It feels right.
There is someone there.
The waters were active.
Start around the feet.
Small cuts.
Well. the other one.
No.
Beautiful.
Okay. now Let's
disassemble the front.
Empty your belly.
Good morning my baby.
Watch this.
That's right.
This is it.
You do the other one.
Tutu.
You are a brave young man.
Thank you. Sister.
Are you hungry. Arthur?
I'm hungry. Sister.
Sarah will cook you a nice
dinner tonight. Herring stew.
Did you like this?
Where do you come from. Arthur?
My family's farm is on the Keswick side.
- Keswick. huh?
- Yes sir.
-Randolph.
- Keswick side.
- The leper says he is looking for his nephew.
- Yes.
- Were you attacked?
- It happened.
- On the way?
Yes.
- We are safe here.
- Which road?
Road to Keswick. sir.
Thank God you were saved.
I thank God.
Since you're so brave. how about
eating pears with honey after dinner?
Thank you. Sister.
Little Margaret...
A man Arthur... Have you ever seen
him before you came to the Order?
Margaret.
Guys...
The men who hurt your father...
Have you seen their faces?
My father told me to run away.
My father stopped praying..
He was angry.
He prayed in his heart.
What was my father's name?
Your father is your father.
Bring him here.
Oh. that's good work.
Do you see it supporting a fold here?
Now you need to balance
this. So it bends evenly.
So this part here needs to be thin.
Is it ok?
Can you do it for me?
I will make you a bow.
Certainly.
Today I remembered the
story of a poet named Lucretius.
He wrote about things called atoms.
If you separate trees.
people and stones from
each other. they are
They turn into the
smallest. indivisible parts that make up everything.
And these atoms are floating in space.
And sometimes they change
their route for no reason.
The smallest amount. not even a hair's breadth.
And their atoms start to intersect and intertwine with each other.
If it weren't for that small. unforeseen change that forced
nothing under the heavens would exist.
Fine. you're fine.
Stronger.
This is it.
Good morning my baby.
Stop it.
Good. here we go.
Good morning my baby.
Which one are you considering for streaming?
Let's take a look.
Ok.
Here you go.
Both are good.
Margaret.
Margaret. come play.
Arthur.
- Do you know how to set a trap?
- Yes.
Good morning my baby.
I need a strong hand.
Does your family own land?
Yes.
How many of you are there?
I don't know.
Are you okay?
I... I'm not as young as I once was.
What I need is some support.
Thank you.
They dealt you a big blow.
- Yes.
- Who did it?
A man.
Some guys.
Bandits.
A man?
Bandits?
- Yes.
- Can I have a look?
It's quite a blow.
You're lucky to be alive.
- You are a lucky kid.
- Yes.
You should be
grateful to be alive.
Yes..It was a long stick.
You're lucky he didn't
blow your head off.
Randolph!
Moshe!
The priest told us to come.
Are you in a lot of pain?
Do you remember trees?
Pears. apples and elderberries.
Wonderful.
You know that you are the most important
person in little Margaret's life.
I am not important.
Think of all the people
whose lives you intersect with.
We were important to all of them in some way.
Guy of Gisborne and Robin Hood
Do you know its story?
Yes.
They say you killed him.
Did you really cut off his head?
You're confused. Leper.
I won't tell anyone.
But don't lie to a
man on his deathbed.
So... did you really cut off his head?
There was no Guy from Gisborne.
Just one of many
tales passed down.
But I cut off the others' heads.
Do you really not remember?
No.
Consider this name.
There was a man from Gisborne.
But you didn't cut off his head.
You cut off his ear.
You said you'd share a
drink with him in another life.
Do you remember this?
It's like we found a different life.
Now... There is a cruelty
that I would like you not to do...
And you will protect
the orchard until you die.
You will serve the Priest and the people of this place...
Sect. past and future.
But at no point in time.
In those beautiful and peaceful years...
Will you tell the Priest
who you really are?
From where?
Because...
One of those nameless. faceless people...
That death in the shadows of your mind...
in another life...
was his beloved.
Promise me.
Robin.
Goodbye. Brigid.
Arthur.
Come on.
There is a child on the far shore.
Maybe it's your nephew.
The leper said he was
looking for his missing nephew.
Yes.
- Could it be him?
- We'll see.
I don't see any traces of anyone.
We must wait.
Maybe they'll come back.
What is your name?
Arthur.
Don't waste your time lying to me.
What is your real name?
Godwyn.
You decide. Godwyn; Will you do
the work yourself or bring your family?
For what job?
How many men have you killed. Godwyn?
How many children did you kill?
I've killed so many
people I can't count them.
For longer than your life; whom I killed a lifetime ago; and
actually I don't even know who he is; I kill people's descendants.
That's me then The ones
that have no meaning for you.
But their siblings and their children
and grandchildren remember me.
And now I must kill them.
Over and over again...
in different forms.
like shadows... again.
And yet it never ends.
It's a curse. Godwyn.
This is something you brought upon
yourself. even if it was done out of duty.
He doesn't care about your duty.
All this world cares about is blood...
and will give in return The
only thing is blood again.
You want to kill a child. Godwin?
Do you want to take responsibility
for the murder of a little girl?
No.
Is your father dead?
What about your uncles?
Only I remained.
Who else lives. Godwyn?
My mother.
My aunts.
My sisters.
You have a home. Godwyn.
- Yes.
- Go home.
Tell your family that all your
blood debts have been paid.
It will all be paid for one day.
Sleep in your own bed.
Value the life you will
share with your loved ones.
And if you come back here...
You'll be wasting this chance
at life that I'm giving you now
and I will cut your throat.
I will never think about it again.
Go now.
Don't look back.
I thought you were gone.
I am an outlaw
My Robin.
You should know that I'm a monster.
I'm not one of the Randolphs.
I am an outlaw...
Robin Hood
Turkish subtitles;
ufukbaba
I am sad.
Tell me how I should leave.
I will go now.
Get into bed.
- Brigid.
- Lie down..
You burned my husband alive.
I dream that he is already dead.
But why did you bar the door?
Searching for the ashes of
our home seemed like a lifetime.
And it looked so small.
curled up in the corner.
with most of it gone.
And I can't imagine it
enough. I know you're alive.
Because he hugged
our children until the end.
Randolph.
Mine.
People talk about Robin Hood...
They tell stories..
It's all lies.
Lies I told a long time ago...
So these fools...
They followed me into the dark.
Robin.
What are they doing to you?
Don't be afraid.
I will save you from this place.
I will save little Margaret.
We will start a
new life together.
Edward
Tell me about your wife.
My wife...
Margaret.
My wife Margaret.
Draw a portrait.
Should I draw a portrait?
He has hair...
It's like red...
setting sun.
Like the setting summer sun.
Red... like a sinking summer...
Sun...
Robin...
Did you find your correct death?
I'm ready to finish.
I owe this life to you.
Monstrous...
But I owe this life to you.
You don't owe me anything.
I've never taken a life before.
It can be like pruning a flower.
Ok.
It shouldn't be.
But it could happen.
I help those who
come to this island.
I am healing them.
Please.
Heal me.
Little Margaret...
Your father's name was John.
I've known him for many years.
before he became your father.
One day a fast flowing
I was crossing a
bridge over the river.
I met him...
He was stubborn.
He would not surrender.
Not to anyone.
Not even to me.
We also wrestled on that bridge.
He's hitting back and forth.
I hit him on the side of his head.
He hit me in the stomach.
I stumbled on that bridge.
I fell into the water.
He dropped me on my butt.
When I drag myself out...
I was soaked to the bone...
We hugged.
We named your father Little John.
And the outlaws in Greenwood
As. we have lived for many years...
We had holidays.
We gave silver to the humble.
But we stole that silver.
her bad
We stole from people...
Do you understand?
Bad people.
Your father...
He wanted me to tell you...
Because he loved you very much. my dear.
You should never tell anyone.
Even to the kids you play with.
You should never tell them your father's name.
There are bad people out there.
And they're angry at your father.
That's why they're angry at you too.
Can we keep this secret?
I can keep this
secret Little Margaret.
Can you?
Good morning my baby.
Come to me now.
Take this.
Why did they call it small?
What?
Why was my father called "Little"?
Because it was small when I found it.
Like you.
String it up.
Bend with your leg.
like you see me do.
Go to the window.
Insert the arrow into the bowstring.
Find a spot where the
waters meet the sky.
Read it to the fullest...
And wait.
I'll tell you when to relax.
And when I do this...
you don't let go...
You don't even hold it anymore.
Watch out for that target.
Your body will always be in motion.
Feel when the arrow will fly correctly.
You will find a dance.
Wait until I tell you to quit...
You are strong.
Feel...
Don't swing...
That dance...
Now relax.